(soothing music)
♪ And all I am is a man ♪
♪ I want the world in my hands ♪
♪ I hate the beach but I stand ♪
♪ In California with my toes in the sand ♪
♪ Use the sleeves of my sweater ♪
♪ Let's have an adventure ♪
♪ Head in the clouds, but
my gravity's centered ♪
♪ Touch my neck and I'll touch yours ♪
♪ You in those little
high-waisted shorts, oh ♪
♪ She knows what I think about ♪
♪ And what I think about ♪
♪ One love, two mouths ♪
♪ One love, one house ♪
♪ No shirt, no blouse ♪
♪ Just us, you find out ♪
♪ Nothing that I wouldn't
wanna tell you about, no ♪
♪ 'Cause it's too cold ♪
♪ For you here and now ♪
♪ So let me hold ♪
♪ Both your hands in the
holes of my sweater ♪
♪ And if I may just
take your breath away ♪
♪ I don't mind if
there's not much to say ♪
♪ Sometimes the silence guides our minds ♪
♪ So move to a place so far away ♪
♪ The goosebumps start to raise ♪
♪ The minute that my left
hand meets your waist ♪
♪ And then I watch your face ♪
♪ Put my finger on your tongue ♪
♪ 'Cause you love to taste, yeah ♪
♪ These hearts adore ♪
♪ Everyone the other beats hardest for ♪
♪ Inside this place is warm ♪
♪ Outside it starts to pour ♪
♪ Coming down ♪
♪ One love, two mouths ♪
♪ One love, one house ♪
♪ No shirt, no blouse ♪
♪ Just us, you find out ♪
♪ Nothing that I wouldn't wanna
tell you about, no, no, no ♪
♪ 'Cause it's too cold ♪
♪ For you here and now ♪
♪ So let me hold ♪
♪ Both your hands in the
holes of my sweater ♪
♪ 'Cause it's too cold ♪
♪ For you here and now ♪
♪ So let me hold ♪
♪ Both your hands in the
holes of my sweater, whoa ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa ♪
♪ 'Cause it's too cold ♪
♪ For you here and now ♪
♪ So let me hold ♪
♪ Both your hands in the
holes of my sweater ♪
♪ It's too cold ♪
♪ For you here and now ♪
♪ Let me hold ♪
♪ Both your hands in the
holes of my sweater ♪
♪ And it's too cold ♪
♪ It's too cold ♪
♪ The holes of my sweater ♪